// mock questions for now
var questions = [
  {
    qid : 1,
    question: 'Mario Kart is a video game series publish by which company?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'Electronic Arts',
      b: 'Nintendo',
      c: 'Sony',
      d: 'Activision Blizzard'
    },
    answer:'Nintendo'
  },
  {
    qid : 2,
    question: 'If a liquor is 100 proof how much alcohol does it contain by percentage?',
    answerList: {
      a: '100 percent',
      b: '70 percent',
      c: '30 percent',
      d: '50 percent'
    },
    answer:'50 percent'
  },
  {
    qid : 3,
    question: 'In the poker game Texas Holdâ€™em, how many cards are dealt to each player?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'One',
      b: 'Seven',
      c: 'Two',
      d: 'Four'
    },
    answer:'Two'
  },
  {
    qid : 4,
    question: 'What international event for athletes with disabilities is held in the same years and cities as the Olympic Games?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'America\'s Cup',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Pan American Games',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'The Paralympic Games'
  },
  {
    qid : 5,
    question: 'What Greek mathematician is considered the founder and father of Geometry?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'Euclid',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Pan American Games',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'Euclid'
  },
  {
    qid : 6,
    question: 'What is the name of the dog from the 1960s television cartoon The Jetsons?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'America\'s Cup',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Astro',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'Astro'
  },
  {
    qid : 7,
    question: 'What is the heaviest naturally occurring element found on Earth?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'America\'s Cup',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Pan American Games',
      d: 'Uranium (U92)'
    },
    answer:'Uranium (U92)'
  },
  {
    qid : 8,
    question: 'Which book holds the record of being the most stolen book from public libraries?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'America\'s Cup',
      b: 'Guinness Book of World Records',
      c: 'Pan American Games',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'Guinness Book of World Records'
  },
  {
    qid : 9,
    question: 'What is the closest star to our own sun?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'Proxima Centauri',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Pan American Games',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'Proxima Centauri'
  },
  {
    qid : 10,
    question: 'What is the name for the longest side of a right triangle?' ,
    answerList: {
      a: 'America\'s Cup',
      b: 'The Paralympic Games',
      c: 'Hypotenuse',
      d: 'World Cup'
    },
    answer:'Hypotenuse'
  },
]